

MOHAMMED A. ALNAHAL

Date of birth: 18/06/2000

Nationality: Palestinian (Autonomous Palestinian Territories)

Gender: Male

CONTACT

RAFAH, Omar bin al-Khattab Street 00970 RAFAH, Autonomous Palestinian Territories

mahmoudalielnahal@gmail.c om

(+972) 972597563442

ABOUT ME

I'm a software engineer and back-end developer, and I mainly work with PHP/ Laravel

I have over three years of web development experience, working on developing, testing and improving web applications.

The applications have a responsive design, high performance, clean and quality code, readable code, and reusable components. highly motivated. We constantly strive to improve performance. Familiar and expert in web application engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

04/2000 - CURRENT

Freelancer

I am working as a freelancer.

I have built and developed many PHP / Laravel applications in different fields such as:

E-commerce application.

Photo Gallery.

Delivery application.

Movies application.

And many other applications.

07/2020 – 02/2021 – Rafah, Autonomous Palestinian Territories

Rafah City Municipality

trainee IT. developer

I worked in IT department as a data entry and web interface developer I also developed a few websites

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages:

JavaScript.

JAVA

HTML

CSS

PHP/Laravel

UI/UX

SQL/SQL+

Flutter/Dart

UML

C/C++

Libraries & frameworks:

Laravel

Google Map.

Familiar with APIs.

React

Control System:

Git.

GitHub.

KEYS SKILLS

Key Skills

Dealing UI Designing.

Coding.

Clean & Quality code.

Debugging.

Performance Improvement.

Webpage Optimization.

Project Delivery.

Client Surviving.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

15/07/2018 - CURRENT

Software Engineering

Al-Azhar University-Gaza (AUG)

http://www.alazhar.edu.ps/

05/04/2019 - 10/08/2019

front end developer

Gaza Sky Geeks

https://gazaskygeeks.com/

01/2022 - CURRENT

back end developer

W3school

https://www.w3schools.com/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Arabic

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening B1	Reading B2	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	Writing B2
		B1	B1	

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Excel / Zoom / Social Media / Google Drive / LinkedIn / Team-work oriented / Analytical skills / VS Code / Internet Search / Analytical Thinking / Power Point / Excellent writing and verbal communication skills / Good time management / ocial Media (Instagram Facebook YouTube Twitter)